{
    "id": "e27d4a6d18fe453397e67f92651f660e",
    "title": "Inversion",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I wondered what time …………………… starting.",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the auxiliary verb goes after the subject.",
            "answers": [
                "was the show",
                "the show was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "31ebd846bb1a42cf99b5d7f258eb7f3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me what ……………………….. thinking about.",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the auxiliary verb goes after the subject.",
            "answers": [
                "was I",
                "I was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7bb67a063c684165a6443059aead5861"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wondered who ………………………",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the auxiliary verb goes after the subject.",
            "answers": [
                "had left the door open",
                "the door had left open"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b2862a7ba6ea4f86afacdc121be55bb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What a lovely place ………………………….!",
            "description": "The auxiliary verb usually goes after the subject in exclamations with how and what.",
            "answers": [
                "is Shimla",
                "Shimla is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "50aaa6e1deeb4d97a8ebeeea069ee4b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "How beautiful ………………………..!",
            "description": "The auxiliary verb usually goes after the subject in exclamations with how and what.",
            "answers": [
                "are the flowers",
                "the flowers are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6ca957984494029ab9d8f06335d17c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "At no time ………………………….. aware of what was happening.",
            "description": "If a negative expression comes at the beginning of a clause, it is usually followed by auxiliary verb + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "he was",
                "was he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d360b1961a894d94a166f542dbd21556"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hardly ……………………… arrived when trouble started.",
            "description": "Inversion is common after words like hardly, seldom, rarely, little or never.",
            "answers": [
                "had he",
                "he had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81227bdf90b14c3c92031faa7f6b7a03"
        },
        {
            "question": "Never ……………………….. seen such a mess.",
            "description": "Inversion is common after words like hardly, seldom, rarely, little or never.",
            "answers": [
                "I have",
                "have I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1e78552698aa44b980b11ffd2fa886ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "Little ……………………….. what she was doing",
            "description": "Inversion is common after words like hardly, seldom, rarely, little or never.",
            "answers": [
                "did she realize",
                "she realized"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b76fa3c95bee44c69f44eda845752c60"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only then ………………………… what I had done.",
            "description": "When only comes at the beginning of the sentence, it is followed by an inverted word order. ",
            "answers": [
                "did I understand",
                "I understood"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c48fb7f4a054527b0d62507feddc9f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not only ………………………. our money, but we were nearly kidnapped.",
            "description": "When not only comes at the beginning of the sentence, it is followed by an inverted word order. ",
            "answers": [
                "we lost",
                "lost we",
                "did we lose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "16db268630b64ff993bf4b6402ae9b69"
        },
        {
            "question": "What a lovely morning ……………………….!",
            "description": "The auxiliary verb usually goes after the subject in exclamations with how and what.",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "it is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d4f4457b29e421ca6cc03941f101b26"
        }
    ]
}